Love is timeless.
The Age of Adaline is a romance, fantasy, drama
film directed by Lee Toland Krieger.
After 29-year-old Adaline recovers from a nearly lethal
accident, she inexplicably stops growing older.
As the years stretch on and on, Adaline keeps her secret to
herself  until she meets a man who changes her life.
Adaline Bowman, played by Blake Lively.
Ellis Jones, played by Michiel Huisman.
William Jones, played by Harrison Ford.
Flemming, played by Ellen Burstyn.
Kathy Jones, played by Kathy Baker.
Kikki Jones, played by Amanda Crew.
The Age of Adaline is a 2015 American romantic fantasy film
directed by Lee Toland Krieger and written by J.
Mills Goodloe and Salvador Paskowitz.
The film stars Blake Lively as Adaline, with Michiel Huisman,
Harrison Ford, Kathy Baker, Amanda Crew, and Ellen Burstyn.
Narrated by Hugh Ross, the story follows Adaline Bowman, a young woman who
stops aging following an accident at the age of twenty-nine.
The film was produced by Sidney Kimmel
Entertainment and Lakeshore Entertainment.
Principal photography took place in Vancouver from March 5 to May 5, 2014.
It premiered in New York City on April 19, 2015, and was cinematically
released on April 24 in the United States by Lionsgate.
It received mixed reviews from critics, though many praised both Lively's and Ford's
performances, citing them as some of their best work in recent years.
A modest box-office success, it grossed $65.7 million
worldwide on a $25 million budget.
The film received two nominations at the 42nd Saturn Awards, one for
Best Fantasy Film and one for Lively for Best Actress.
The film explores themes of immortality, san
francisco, california, love, forever.
The tone is emotional.